{
	"network_services": {
		"0": {
			"question": "Which of these is a layer two protocol",
			"options": [
				"DNS",
				"DHCP",
				"ARP",
				"RIP"
			],
			"answer": "ARP"
		},
		"1": {
			"question": "Which of these hands out IP addresses dynamically",
			"options": [
				"DNS",
				"DHCP",
				"IP",
				"Static"
			],
			"answer": "DHCP"
		},
		"2": {
			"question": "Which of these converts IP addresses to a readable format",
			"options": [
				"DNS",
				"ARP",
				"IP",
				"Static"
			],
			"answer": "DNS"
		},
		"3": {
			"question": "How does ARP talk to computers at layer 2",
			"options": [
				"Multicast",
				"Dualcast",
				"Broadcast",
				"Unicast"
			],
			"answer": "Braodcast"
		}
	},
	"network_types": {
		"0": {
			"question": "Which of these branches from a single point",
			"options": [
				"Star",
				"Ring",
				"Mesh",
				"Bus"
			],
			"answer": "Star"
		},
		"1": {
			"question": "Which of these is the most resilliant",
			"options": [
				"Bus",
				"Mesh",
				"Star",
				"Ring"
			],
			"answer": "Mesh"
		},
		"2": {
			"question": "Which of these converts IP addresses to a readable format",
			"options": [
				"DNS",
				"ARP",
				"IP",
				"Static"
			],
			"answer": "DNS"
		},
		"3": {
			"question": "How does ARP talk to computers at layer 2",
			"options": [
				"Multicast",
				"Dualcast",
				"Broadcast",
				"Unicast"
			],
			"answer": "Broadcast"
		}
	},
	"firewalls": {
		"0": {
			"question": "Which of these checks the state of packet",
			"options": [
				"Stateless",
				"Statefull",
				"Switch",
				"Load Balancer"
			],
			"answer": "Statefull"
		},
		"1": {
			"question": "Which of these exists at the application layer",
			"options": [
				"Application level Gateway",
				"Stateful multilayer",
				"Circuit Level",
				"Router"
			],
			"answer": "Application level Gateway"
		},
		"2": {
			"question": "Which of these can be found at the session layer",
			"options": [
				"Application level gateway",
				"Circuit level gateway",
				"Modem",
				"Access Point"
			],
			"answer": "Circuit level gateway"
		},
		"3": {
			"question": "Which of these actions does a firewall perform",
			"options": [
				"Inspect Packets",
				"Route Packets",
				"Block Packets",
				"Drop Packets"
			],
			"answer": "Route Packets"
		}
	},
	"common_attacks": {
		"0": {
			"question": "Which of these can self replicate",
			"options": [
				"Virus",
				"Worm",
				"Ransomware",
				"Trojan Horse"
			],
			"answer": "Worm"
		},
		"1": {
			"question": "Which of these disguises itself as a useful program?",
			"options": [
				"Virus",
				"Worm",
				"Ransomware",
				"Trojan Horse"
			],
			"answer": "Trojan Horse"
		},
		"2": {
			"question": "Which of these locks down a pc to extort money",
			"options": [
				"Virus",
				"Worm",
				"Ransomware",
				"Trojan Horse"
			],
			"answer": "Ransomware"
		},
		"3": {
			"question": "What is the most common type of malware",
			"options": [
				"Virus",
				"Worm",
				"Ransomware",
				"Trojan Horse"
			],
			"answer": "Virus"
		}
	}
}